Photographs Archival Collection 6038 P
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Photographs Archival Collection
1973-2000
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives
6038 P
12.5 cubic feet
12.5 linear ft.
Photographs.
8072103
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, June 26, 2013
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, October 29, 2015
Scope and Contents
This is a varied collection of photographs from many events and celebrations for the ILR School. Included are photographs from the library, student activities, award dinners, Conferences, faculty meetings, as well as photographs of each Dean of the school.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
8072103
- 25/0 - Joint Legislative Committee on Industrial and Labor Conditions (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  10 photographs
- 25/0 - Joint Legislative Committee on Industrial & Labor Conditions - Negatives (Box 1, Folder 2)
- 25/1 - Board of Temporary Trustees (Box 1, Folder 3)
  2 photographs
- 25/2 - Council of the School (Box 1, Folder 4)
  12 photographs
- 25/3/A - Faculty Group Photographs - 1940's (Box 1, Folder 5)
  16 photographs
- 25/3/A - Faculty Group Photographs - 1940's (Box 1, Folder 6)
  15 photographs
- 25/3/A - Faculty (Group Photographs) - 1950's (Box 1, Folder 7)
  17 photographs
- 25/3/A - Faculty (Group Photographs) - 1960's (Box 1, Folder 8)
  21 photographs
- 25/3/A - Faculty Group Photographs (1960's) (Box 1, Folder 9)
  19 photographs
- 25/3/A - Faculty Group Photos - 1970's (Box 1, Folder 10)
- 25/3/A - Faculty Group Photos (Box 1, Folder 11)
  3 photographs
- 25/3/A - Faculty Group Photos (Box 1, Folder 12)
- 25/3/A - Faculty Group Photos (Box 1, Folder 13)
- 25/3/A - Faculty Group Photos (negatives) (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Faculty Individual Photographs (A-C) (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Faculty individual Photographs (A-C) (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Faculty Individual Photographs (D-H) (Box 2, Folder 3)
  30 photographs
- Faculty Individual Photographs (I-O) (Box 2, Folder 4)
  18 photographs
- Faculty Individual Photographs (P-S) (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Faculty Individual Photographs (T-Z) (Box 2, Folder 6)
  8 photographs
- Faculty (M.P.Catherwood) (Box 2, Folder 7)
  20 photographs
- ILR Faculty Negatives (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Faculty - Unknown - 9 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  6 photographs
- Deans - Group Shots (Box 2, Folder 10)
  5 photographs
- Dean's - M.P. Catherwood (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Deans - Irving Ives (Box 2, Folder 12)
  22 photographs
- Deans - Lawler (Box 2, Folder 13)
  1
- Deans - Lipsky (Box 2, Folder 14)
  7 photographs
- Deans - McConnell (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Deans - McKersie (Box 2, Folder 16)
  1 photograph
- Deans - Moore (Box 2, Folder 17)
  25 photographs
- Deans - Neufeld (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Deans - Robert Risley (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Deans - Bob Smith (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Resident Instruction - Class 1 Photographs - 1947-1948 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  24 photographs
- Resident Instruction (Class Photographs) -- 1947-1948 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  23 photographs
- Resident Instruction (Class Photographs) 1947-1948 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Resident Instruction (Class Photographs) 1940's-1960's (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Resident Instruction (Class Photographs) 1940's-1960's (Box 3, Folder 5)
  13 photographs
- Resident Instruction (Class Photographs) 1940's-1970's (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Resident Instruction (Class Photographs) 1940's-1970's (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Resident Instruction - Negatives - 4x5 - 1949-1952 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- 25/5/B - President Instruction (Photographs of prominent guest lecturers) (1947-1958) (Box 4, Folder 1)
- 25/5/B - Resident Instruction (Photographs of Prominent Guest Lecturers) 1947-1958 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- 25/5/B - Resident Instruction (Photographs of Prominent guest Lecturers) 1947-1958 (negatives & photographs) (Box 4, Folder 3)
- 25/5/C Resident Instruction (Field Trips) 1947-1956 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  28 photographs
- 25/5/C Resident Instruction (Field Trips) 1947-1956 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- 25/5/C Resident Instruction (Field Trips) 1947-1952 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- 25/5/C Resident Instruction (Field Trips) 1947-1959 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- 25/5/C Residential Instruction (Field Trips) 1947-1959 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- 25/5/C Residential Instructor (Field Trips) 1947-1959 (negatives & photographs) (Box 4, Folder 9)
  37 photographs
- Classes at Buffalo-February 1947 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  14 photographs
- Classes at Buffalo - February 1947 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Classes at Niagara Falls -- 2/1947 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Classes at Auburn - 2/1947 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Training Directors Conference - August 1947 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Ithaca High School - February 1947 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Labor Management Conference - August 1947 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Labor Management Conference - August 1947 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Amalgamated Clothing Wkrs. - Rochester, 1947 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Dr. Smith's Class at Binghamton - 1946 and 1947 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Visual Aids Course - March 1947 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Classes at Ithaca - 4/1948 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Ithaca Gun Co. - Group at Chanticleer - 4/1948 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Extension Teachers Conference - June 5, 1948 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  4 photographs
- Training Directors Conference - July 1948 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Local 7, ACWA-CIO Classes - Albany 5/1948 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Labor Economics Conference - August 1948 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- ILR Conference at Willard Straight - 11/5/1948 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Conference for Research on Mgt. 12/9-10/1948 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Communication Wkrs. Of America (Box 6, Folder 1)
- S - Syracuse - 3/1949 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Ithaca Gun Co. - Foreman's Dinner - 2/1949 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Int'l. Brotherhood of Electrical Wkrs. - NY City - 3/1949 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- N.Y. Personnel Management Assn. 3/1949 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Personnel Club of New York 3/1949 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Telephone Employees Org. 3/1949 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Gas, Coke & Chemical Wkrs. 3/1949 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Laundry Wkrs. Jt. Bd. 3/1949 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Local 169 Amalgamated Clothing Wkrs. 3/1949 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- I.A.M. Dist. Meeting 4/1949 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Personnel Mgmt. Seminar Summer 1949 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Benjamin Roberts Class at IBEW, NYC - Spring 1949 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Government Research Conference 3/1949 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Social Security Conference 6/1949 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Union Workshop -- AFL-Federal Unions 7/1949 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- American Hospitals Assn. Conf. 7/1949 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- American Society of Safety Engineers 11/1949 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  9 photographs
- Classes at New York City - Spring 1949 (Box 6, Folder 19)
- AFL Conference at Cornell Spring 1949 (Box 6, Folder 20)
- Training Directors Conference July 1949 (Box 6, Folder 21)
- Conf. on Teaching of Labor Economics 9/1949 (Box 6, Folder 22)
- Extension Course, Albany, NY (Box 6, Folder 23)
- Ansco Foremen's Assn. Course 1/1949 (Box 6, Folder 24)
- health, Welfare + Pensions (4/1950) (Box 7, Folder 1)
- IAM Local Lodge (Certificates) - Feb. 1950 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Class at Glenn Falls, Feb. 27, 1950 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Steelworkers Conference 7/1950 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Students from Oswego Teachers College 5/1950 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- American Federation of Labor - July 1950 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  11 photographs
- Social Security Conf. - May 1950 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Extension Teachers Conf. - 5/1950 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Hospital Conference - 7/19-14/1950 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  1 photographs
- Class for New York city Statler Hotel 6/1951 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Joint Legislative Committee on Housing and Multiple Dwelling - Aug. 1950 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Teachers Conference - 9/14-16/1950 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Extension Teachers Conference - 5/1951 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- I.A.M. - 3/1951 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Conference on Wage Surveys - June 1951 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- Industrial Education -- 7/10-12/1951 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- Training Directors -- 7/12-13/1951 (Box 7, Folder 17)
- U. Steelworkers - CIO -- 7/15-22/1951 (Box 7, Folder 18)
- Macy's S-1 Local -- 7/20-21/1951 (Box 7, Folder 19)
- Training Institute - 7/16-20/1951 (Box 7, Folder 20)
- First Prof. Conf. for Ind. And Technical Course Teachers (Emerson) 7/1950 (Box 7, Folder 21)
- Wage & Salary Admin. 7/23-25/1951 (Box 7, Folder 22)
- I.A.M. Conference (Machinists) 23 7/1951 (Box 7, Folder 23)
- N.Y.S. Savings Bank Assoc. 8/1-3/1951 (Box 7, Folder 24)
- Social Security Conf. 9/1951 (Box 7, Folder 25)
- Amer. Society of Safety Engineers, Fall 1951 (Box 7, Folder 26)
- Conf. of Christians & Jews 7/26-28/1951 (Box 7, Folder 27)
- Hospital Administrators Conf. 10/1951 (Box 7, Folder 28)
- Conf. on Employee Association Wage Surreys 12/1951 (Box 7, Folder 29)
- Miscellaneous (Box 7, Folder 30)
- Ardemis Kouzian Series (Spring 1952) (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Training Directors Conference 6/1952 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Training Specialists 7/1952 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Labor Union Conf. 7/1952 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Newspapermen's Conference 11/1952 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Profit Sharing Conf. May 21-22, 1953 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Bigelow-Sanford Graduation June 3-5, 1953 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- U.A.W. Conference, June 17-20, 1953 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Training Directors conference July 1953 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  3
- One Week Seminars Summer of 1953 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Steelworkers conf. July 12-18, 1953 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- N.Y.S. Savings Bank Conf. 8/1953 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Arbitration Conf. 1954 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Community Relations Conf. Summer 1954 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Steelworkers Conf. 7/1954 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- Training Directors Conf. Oct. 1954 (Box 8, Folder 16)
- Indian Group October 1954 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  12
- Waterfront Seminar *Seafarers 12/1954 (Box 8, Folder 18)
- Editor - Management Conf. 10/1955 (Box 8, Folder 19)
- Steelworkers Conf. 1955 (Box 8, Folder 20)
- N.Y.S. Safety Inspections Conf. 4&5/1956 (Box 8, Folder 21)
- Seminar on conf. Leadership -- 6/1956 (Box 8, Folder 22)
- In-Plant Communications Conf. 7/1955 (Box 8, Folder 23)
- American Airlines Program 1955 (Box 8, Folder 24)
- 1955 Summer Session, Industrial Education (Box 8, Folder 25)
- Educational Methods Conf. July 1956 (Box 8, Folder 26)
- Steelworkers Aug. 1956 (Box 8, Folder 27)
- Practitioners from field of ILR Short Course 1956-1957 (Box 8, Folder 28)
- Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen & Enginemen - 1957 (Box 8, Folder 29)
- Steelworkers - 1957 (Box 8, Folder 30)
- Machinists - NE Territory -- Summer 1957 (Box 8, Folder 31)
- American Paper & Pulp -- 1958 (Box 8, Folder 32)
- New York Central Railroad Conf. 4/1958 (Box 8, Folder 33)
- Conf. on American Labor's Role in less Developed Countries 10/1958 (Box 8, Folder 34)
- IBEW Conf. Local 3 -- 1956 (Box 8, Folder 35)
- State, County & Municipal Emp. Conf. 7/1958 (Box 8, Folder 36)
- Weinberg Seminar - 1959 (Box 8, Folder 37)
- Abe Silverstein talking to ILR 351 Students May 1958 (Box 8, Folder 38)
- Miscellaneous 1947-1962 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Misc. Extension Pictures taken in other Cities (Box 9, Folder 2)
- 1st Graduation -Labor-Liberal Arts - 1970 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- MILE Pictures - 1961? (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Local Gov't Program 1972 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- A.S.P.A. - 1973 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- IBEW Conf (Frances Perkins) Summer 1960 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- ILR School's Labor Adv. Comm. (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Labor Studies 1973 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Mgmt. Legislative Conf. (Box 9, Folder 10)
- L-M Conf. (Buffalo 1976) (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Prices, Pay & Prod. Conf. 1973 (Box 9, Folder 12)
- IAM Arb. Inst. (1973) (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Steingut Award 1978 (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Und. Black Labor Leaders Conf. (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Buffalo Labor Studies - Orientation Luncheon - 1972 (Box 9, Folder 16)
- Placement Seminars (Donovan, Ross, Hutter) (Box 9, Folder 17)
- Nassau Co. Productivity (Box 9, Folder 18)
- N.Y.C. Central Labor Council (Box 9, Folder 19)
- Union & Mgmt. Placement Reception 1979 (Box 9, Folder 20)
- Conference Photos -- 1967 (Box 9, Folder 21)
- Conference Photos - 25/6-a CWA Leadership Conference 1972 (Box 9, Folder 22)
- Conference Photos - Gen. 25/6-b - 1972 Steelworkers Summer Conference District 4 (Box 9, Folder 23)
- Conference Photos - Gen. - 25/6-C - National Mediation Board Conference, May 1972 (Box 9, Folder 24)
- Conferences - Gen. 25/6-d Frances Perkins - I.B.E.W. Conference - 1960 (Box 9, Folder 25)
- Conference Photos - gen. 25/6-f - ILR Extension Conferences (for Labor Inst. Of the United Steelworkers, 'A Seminar in Counseling Technique', CWA, United Steelworkers) (Box 9, Folder 26)
- Conference Photos - Gen.-2516-g -- Rochester Conferences (IVE) - 1969-1971 (Box 9, Folder 27)
- Conference Photos - Gen. 25/6-h Photos from file #7110 - Exec. Dev. Program - Management Training Program held at Cornell (Box 9, Folder 28)
- Conference Photos - Gen - 25/6-I from photo file - #70-11-6 (Box 9, Folder 29)
- National Institute of Labor Education (NILE) Summer 1961 + 1962 (Box 9.1, Folder 1)
- Weinberg Seminar -- 1965 (Box 9.1, Folder 2)
- More Weinberg Seminars - 25/6 (Box 9.1, Folder 3)
- Weinberg Seminar (Box 9.1, Folder 4)
- Weinberg Seminars (Box 9.1, Folder 5)
- Wilhelm Weinberg - L-M Seminar 10/1961 (Box 9.1, Folder 6)
- Israeli Conference 1/1972 (Box 9.1, Folder 7)
  29 photographs
- Israeli Conference 1/1972 (Box 9.1, Folder 8)
  29 photographs [originally in folder 7]
- Groat Award Dinner 1971-1972 (Box 9.1, Folder 9)
  16 photographs [originally in folder 8]
- Groat Dinner - 1973 (Box 9.1, Folder 10)
  6 photographs [originally in folder 9]
- Groat Dinner - 1974 (Box 9.1, Folder 11)
  13 photographs [originally in folder 10]
- Groat Dinner - 1975, 1976 (Box 9.1, Folder 12)
  3 photographs [originally in folder 11]
- Groat Dinner - 1977 (Box 9.1, Folder 13)
  22 photographs [originally in folder 12]
- Groat Dinner - 1978 (Box 9.1, Folder 14)
  22 photographs [originally in folder 13]
- Groat Dinner - 1979, 1980 (Box 9.1, Folder 15)
  4 photographs [originally in folder 14]
- Publications and School Relations (includes Research) -- 25/7/A (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Publications and School Relations (Photographs used in Publications) - 25/7/B (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Library - 25/9 (1) (Box 10, Folder 3)
  26 photographs
- Library - 25/9 (2) (Box 10, Folder 4)
  12 photographs - (these were originally in folder 3, split due to size of folder)
- Library - 25/9 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  8 photographs (these were originally in folder 4)
- Library II - 25/9 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  26 photographs (these were originally in folder 5)
- Library II (2) -- 25/9 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  8 photographs (these were originally in folder 5)
- Library II (Box 10, Folder 8)
  8 photographs (these were originally in folder 6)
- Catherwood Library Focal Brochure Slides (Box 10, Folder 9)
  18 slides (these were originally in folder 7)
- Catherwood Library Focal Brochure Slides (Box 10, Folder 10)
  20 Slides (these were originally in folder 7)
- ILR - 1 -- 1945 (Box 10.1, Folder 1)
- Senior Class Pictures - June 1947 - June 1952 (Box 10.1, Folder 2)
- Students & Student Activities (Box 10.1, Folder 3)
- Students & Student Activities (Box 10.1, Folder 4)
- Students & Student Activities (Box 10.1, Folder 5)
- Students & Student Activities (Box 10.1, Folder 6)
- Students & Student Activities -- Negatives + Prints (Box 10.1, Folder 7)
- Students & Student Activities - Negatives + Prints (Box 10.1, Folder 8)
- Students & Student Activities -- Negatives + Prints (Box 10.1, Folder 9)
- Students & Student Activities -- Negatives + Prints (Box 10.1, Folder 10)
- Students & Student Activities (Box 10.1, Folder 11)
- More Students & Student Activities (Box 10.1, Folder 12)
- More Students & Student Activities (Box 10.1, Folder 13)
  27 photographs
- Alumni (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Alumni (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Alumni (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Alumni II (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Staff (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Staff (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Staff (Box 11, Folder 7)
- ILR - Alumni Activities 1960's (Box 11, Folder 8)
- ILR - Alumni Activities - 1960's (Box 11, Folder 9)
- School Buildings (Quonset Huts) (Box 11, Folder 10)
- School Buildings (Quonset Huts) (Box 11, Folder 11)
- School Buildings (Ives Hall) (Box 11, Folder 12)
- School Buildings (Ives Hall) (Box 11, Folder 13)
  34 photographs
- School Buildings (Ives Hall) (Box 11, Folder 14)
- School Buildings (Conference Center) (Box 11, Folder 15)
- School Buildings (Miscellaneous) (Box 11, Folder 16)
- School Buildings (Miscellaneous) Negatives + Prints (Box 11, Folder 17)
- ILR Building Construction 1960's? (Box 11.1, Folder 1)
- Ives Hall Building Demolition and Early Construction 1995 (Box 11.1, Folder 2)
- ILR Construction 3-4195 (Constance Finlay) (Box 11.1, Folder 3)
- ILR Construction 7/1995 (Richard Strassberg (Box 11.1, Folder 4)
- School Buildings - Demolition - 2/1995 (Box 11.1, Folder 5)
- School Buildings - Renovations - 1994 (Box 11.1, Folder 6)
- School Building Demolition and Construction 1995, 1996 (Box 11.1, Folder 7)
- More School Buildings - Renovations - 1994 (Box 11.1, Folder 8)
- Ives Hall - New Construction 1998 (Box 11.1, Folder 9)
- ILR Construction Photos by John Goddard -- 3/1996 (Box 11.1, Folder 10)
- VITA Meetings (1) (Box 12, Folder 1)
- VITA Meetings (2) (Box 12, Folder 2)
  26 photographs [expanded from folder 1]
- VITA Meetings (3) (Box 12, Folder 3)
  17 photographs [expanded from folder 1]
- Corning (Box 12, Folder 4)
- ILR - 48 - Spring 1950 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Keyserling speaks at Economic Climate Conference 5/9/1958 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Joint Labor - Mgt. (State Builders) Oct. 28-30 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Making a movie using stationery camera (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Unlabeled (Box 12, Folder 9)
- West German Students Spring 1952 (Box 12, Folder 10)
- Turkish Group Summer of 1951 (Box 12, Folder 11)
- 1953 Graduation of West German Students (Box 12, Folder 12)
- Norwegian Group April 1951 (Box 12, Folder 13)
- Danish & French ECA Group visiting school (Box 12, Folder 14)
- German labor Union Leaders Spring 1950 (Box 12, Folder 15)
- Japanese Women (Box 12, Folder 16)
- Indian Group November 1954 (Box 12, Folder 17)
- Misc. D. - photo shoot #1 6732 - Bill Gellerman (Box 12.1, Folder 1)
- Misc. E. - photo shoot #7110 (Box 12.1, Folder 2)
- Misc. F - Photos from the Office of the Dean - 1967 (Box 12.1, Folder 3)
- Misc. G - State Education Officials (neg no 453) - Feb. 1949 (Box 12.1, Folder 4)
- Misc. H - New York State Audio Visual Council Executive Committee (Neg. no. 456) - Oct. 1949 (Box 12.1, Folder 5)
- Misc. I - Rockefeller (Box 12.1, Folder 6)
- Misc. J - meetings & seminars (Box 12.1, Folder 7)
- Misc. K - Group Photos (Box 12.1, Folder 8)
- Misc. L - Unidentified Event (from red view/photo book) (Box 12.1, Folder 9)
- Misc. (Box 12.1, Folder 10)
- Misc. A - photo shoot #70-10-30 (Box 12.1, Folder 11)
- Misc. B - photo shoot #70-11-6 (Box 12.1, Folder 12)
- Misc. C - photo shoot #1375 (Box 12.1, Folder 13)
- Misc. - photo shoot #4241 (Box 12.1, Folder 14)
- KC 50th Anniv. Speakers - Daniel Kheel (Box 13, Folder 1)
- KC 50th Anniv. Speakers - Herb Finch (Box 13, Folder 2)
- KC 50th Anniv. Speakers - Ilene DeVault (Box 13, Folder 3)
- KC 50th Anniv. Speakers - Group (Box 13, Folder 4)
- KC 50th Anniv. Staff Members (1) (Box 13, Folder 5)
- KC 50th Anniv. Staff Members (2) (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Maurice Neufeld & Gordon Law, Kheel Center 50 Anniv. (Box 13, Folder 7)
- KC 50th Anniv. General Reception (Box 13, Folder 8)
- KC 50th Anniv. General Reception (Box 13, Folder 9)
- KC 50th Anniv. Speakers Dean Edward Lawler (Box 13, Folder 10)
- KC 50th Anniv. Speakers - Richard Strassberg (Box 13, Folder 11)
- KC 50th Anniv. Unveiling - Donor Plaque (Box 13, Folder 12)
- Second Annual Institute for Training Specialists - June 10-14, 1952 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- McKelvey, Jean Trepp (Box 13, Folder 14)
  11 photographs -- [2as bx 14, ff1]
- Jean McKelvey and Alice Grant Professorship - 1994 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  18 photographs -- [was bx 14, ff2]
- McKelvey, Jean Trepp "1929 Portrait Directory" (Box 13, Folder 16)
  booklet
- William S. O'Neill (Box 14, Folder 1)
  4 photographs; 5 Certificates
- ILR - June Nildock and William Fowler (1981) (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Construction photos (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Construction site and meeting photos (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Construction site and meeting photos (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Construction site and meeting photos (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Construction site and meeting photos (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Construction related photographs (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Construction related photographs (Box 15, Folder 7)
- Construction related photographs (Box 15, Folder 8)
- Construction related photographs (Box 15, Folder 9)
- Construction related photographs (Box 15, Folder 10)
- Construction related photographs (Box 15, Folder 11)
- Construction related photographs (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Ted + Anne Kheel with Gordon Law (Box 16, Folder 1)
  31 photographs
- Library Breaking Ground - Guest Photos + Negs - 2000 (1) (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Library Breaking Ground - Guest Photos + Negs - 2000 (2) (Box 16, Folder 3)
- Library Tower Dedication - Photos + Negs -- Phase 1 (Box 16, Folder 4)
- Library Tower Dedication - Photos + Negs - Phase 1 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Library Tower Dedication Photos + Negs - Phase 1 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Library Tower Dedication - Photos + Negs - Phase 1 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- Library Tower Dedication - Photos + Negs - Phase 1 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  39 photographs
- Library Tower Dedication - Photos + Negs - Phase 1 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  47 photographs
- Library Tower Dedication - Photos + Negs - Phase 1 (Box 16, Folder 10)
- Kheel Center - Photos + Negs (Box 16, Folder 11)
  38 photographs
- ILR Library Dedication - Photos + Negs (1) (Box 16, Folder 12)
- ILR Library Dedication - Photos (2) (Box 16, Folder 13)
- ILR Library Dedication - Photos (3) (Box 16, Folder 14)
- "Old" Bldg., Library Reference Conference - 1999 (Box 16, Folder 15)
- Library Staff and Building Photos + Negs (Box 16, Folder 16)
- Library Tower Dedication Photos + Negs + Contact Sheets (Box 16, Folder 17)
  36 photographs
- Building Dedication - April 1998 - contacts (Dewey Neild, Photographer) (Box 16, Folder 18)
- Catherwood Library Brochure (Box 16, Folder 19)
- ILR Building Dedication - April 1998 - Harper Conference Room (Box 16, Folder 20)
- ILR Dedication - 1998 (Box 16, Folder 21)
- ILR Dedication 1998 (2) (Box 16, Folder 22)
- ILR Dedication 1998 (3) - Photos + Negs (Box 16, Folder 23)
- Catherwood Library Move 1998 (Box 16, Folder 24)
- ILR at 50 ? (Box 16, Folder 25)
- Unknown (Box 16, Folder 26)
- Office & Classroom Images (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Photo Album contents: ILR Building Dedication (Box 17, Folder 2)
  99 photographs
- Open Hs - Redg Op (Box 17, Folder 3)
- Bob Bluestein/Bill Kay Slides (1) (Box 17, Folder 4)
  20 slides
- Bob Bluestein/Bill Kay Slides (2) (Box 17, Folder 5)
  17 slides
- Bob Bluestein/Bill Kay Slides (3) (Box 17, Folder 6)
- Bob Bluestein/Bill Kay Slides (4) (Box 17, Folder 7)
- Bob Bluestein/Bill Kay Slides (5) (Box 17, Folder 8)
- Photos by Bruce Wang - Contacts + Photos + Negs (Box 17, Folder 9)
- McEntyre Awards - 5/1997 (Box 17, Folder 10)
- McKelvey Dedication (1994) Jon Reis, Photographer (Box 17, Folder 11)
- ILR "Alumni News" Spring 1994 Issue (Box 17, Folder 12)
- Dean Robert Smith (1993) (Box 17, Folder 13)
- Dean Lipsky Farewell (photocopies) (Box 17, Folder 14)
- ILR Graduation 1995? (1) (Box 17, Folder 15)
  27 slides
- ILR Graduation 1995? (2) (Box 17, Folder 16)
  19 slides
- 1996- (Box 17, Folder 17)
- Sheinkman Luncheon (Dewey Neild, Photographer) (Box 17, Folder 18)